[{"answer": "Wow. Enthusiastic 'Hi!', that's beautiful", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Alright, so you're chewing your apple, you got your enthusiastic 'Hi!' Go ahead", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't get the enthusiastic 'Hi!', I'm outta there", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "So, we're talking, and I don't like to go too long before I ask them out, I wanna get it over with right away, so I just blurt out", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Come on, try it. Let me hear you try a Scottish accent", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Irish, Scottish, what's the difference, lassie?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, no, thanks. I can't drink coffee late at night, it keeps me up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "OK", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, I can't begin to tell you how much I hate that commercial", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You like that commercial", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Even if the dialogue did ring true. Even if somehow somewhere men actually talk like that, what does that have to do with the pants? Doesn't that bother you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "But they're talking about nothing", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "But they're talking about nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I know the point", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah, people who work at that place, who're on twent", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I can't call her now, it's too soon. I'm planning a Wednesday call", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's all in your head. All she knows is she had a good time. I think you should call her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, why? I love it when guys call me the next day", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh my friend, do you have any apples", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You told him how I like the commercial", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well, so, you didn't have to tell your friends", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, so what if I said that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I had to tell my friends, my friends didn't have to tell you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "And who makes the switch", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I can't do it. I'll, I'll keep her busy", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What if she sees me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A wuss", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "A signal, right, erm, OK, er OK, the signal is, I'll call out 'Tippy toe!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You don't like 'Tippy toe?", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "'Lemon Tree", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Standard. Micro", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Feel good", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You know, we could go uptown, and that way we could give my friend a ride home", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Don't you wanna go upstairs first", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well they have a phone.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " You know, I think I will go upstairs. I can check my machine", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " You know, I think I will go upstairs. I can check my machine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Phone-Message.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "The bathroom's on the hall to the right", "qsentId": 42}]